<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Data TV Serial -->
    <!-- Poster -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_images">
        <item>@drawable/poster_planetearhii</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_witcher</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_mandalorian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_family_man</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_belive</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_boys</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_when_they_see_us</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_chernobyl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_kota_factory</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_demon_slayer</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Rating -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_ratings">
        <item>9.5</item>
        <item>8.6</item>
        <item>8.8</item>
        <item>8.7</item>
        <item>8.5</item>
        <item>8.8</item>
        <item>9.0</item>
        <item>9.5</item>
        <item>9.2</item>
        <item>8.9</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Title -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_title">
        <item>Planet Earth II</item>
        <item>The Witcher</item>
        <item>The Mandalorian</item>
        <item>The Family Man</item>
        <item>Unbelievable</item>
        <item>The Boys</item>
        <item>When They See Us</item>
        <item>Chernobyl</item>
        <item>Kota Factory</item>
        <item>Demon Slayer: Kimetsu No Yaiba</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Overviews -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_overviews">
        <item>
            David Attenborough returns in this breathtaking documentary showcasing life on Planet Earth.
        </item>
        <item>
            Geralt of Rivia, a solitary monster hunter, struggles to find his place in a world where people often prove more wicked than beasts.
        </item>
        <item>
            The travels of a lone bounty hunter in the outer reaches of the galaxy, far from the authority of the New Republic.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Family Man is an edgy action-drama series, which tells the story of a middle-class man who works for a special cell of the National Investigation Agency. While he tries to protect the nation from terrorists, he also has to protect his family from the impact of his secretive, high-pressure, and low paying job.
        </item>
        <item>
            Based on the true story of Marie, a teenager who was charged with lying about having been raped, and the two female detectives who followed the path to the truth.
        </item>
        <item>
            A group of vigilantes set out to take down corrupt superheroes who abuse their superpowers.
        </item>
        <item>
            Five teens from Harlem become trapped in a nightmare when they\'re falsely accused of a brutal attack in Central Park. Based on the true story.
        </item>
        <item>
            In April 1986, an explosion at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant in the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics becomes one of the world\'s worst man-made catastrophes.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dedicated to Shrimati SL Loney ji, Shri Irodov ji and Maanniya HC Verma ji, \'Kota Factory\' is TVF\'s latest original. India\'s first \'Black and White\' show highlights the problems present day IIT-JEE aspirants face in their day-to-day lives.
        </item>
        <item>
            A family is attacked by demons and only two members survive - Tanjiro and his sister Nezuko, who is turning into a demon slowly. Tanjiro sets out to become a demon slayer to avenge his family and cure his sister.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Storyline -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_storylines">
        <item>
            David Attenborough returns in this breathtaking documentary showcasing life on Planet Earth.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Witcher is an American fantasy drama web television series created by Lauren Schmidt Hissrich for Netflix. It is based on the book series of the same name by Polish writer Andrzej Sapkowski. The Witcher follows the story of Geralt of Rivia, a solitary monster hunter, who struggles to find his place in a world where people often prove more wicked than monsters and beasts. But when destiny hurtles him toward a powerful sorceress, and a young princess with a special gift, the three must learn to navigate independently the increasingly volatile Continent. Written by
        </item>
        <item>
            After the stories of Jango and Boba Fett, another warrior emerges in the Star Wars universe. The Mandalorian is set after the fall of the Empire and before the emergence of the First Order. We follow the travails of a lone gunfighter in the outer reaches of the galaxy far from the authority of the New Republic.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Family Man is an edgy action-drama series, which tells the story of a middle-class man who works for a special cell of the National Investigation Agency. While he tries to protect the nation from terrorists, he also has to protect his family from the impact of his secretive, high-pressure, and low paying job.
        </item>
        <item>
            Based on the true story of Marie, a teenager who was charged with lying about having been raped, and the two female detectives who followed the path to the truth.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Boys is set in a universe where superpowered people are recognized as heroes by the general public and owned by powerful corporation Vought International, which ensures that they are aggressively marketed and monetized. Outside of their heroic personas, most are arrogant and corrupt. The series primarily focuses on two groups: the titular Boys, vigilantes looking to keep the corrupted heroes under control, and the Seven, Vought International\'s premier superhero team. The Boys are led by Billy Butcher, who despises all superpowered people, and the Seven are led by the egotistical and unstable Homelander. As a conflict ensues between the two groups, the series also follows the new members of each team: Hugh "Hughie" Campbell of the Boys, who joins the vigilantes after his girlfriend is killed in a high speed collision by the Seven\'s A-Train, and Annie January / Starlight of the Seven, a young and hopeful heroine forced to face the truth about the heroes she admires.
        </item>
        <item>
            In 1989, a jogger was assaulted and raped in New York\'s Central Park, and five young people were subsequently charged with the crime. The quintet, labeled the Central Park Five, maintained its innocence and spent years fighting the convictions, hoping to be exonerated. This limited series spans a quarter of a century, from when the teens are first questioned about the incident in the spring of 1989, going through their exoneration in 2002 and ultimately the settlement reached with the city of New York in 2014. The cast is full of Emmy nominees and winners, including Michael Kenneth Williams, John Leguizamo, Felicity Huffman, and Blair Underwood. Oscar nominated and Emmy winner Ava DuVernay co-wrote and directed the four episodes.
        </item>
        <item>
            In April 1986, a huge explosion erupted at the Chernobyl nuclear power station in northern Ukraine. This series follows the stories of the men and women, who tried to contain the disaster, as well as those who gave their lives preventing a subsequent and worse one.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dedicated to Shrimati SL Loney ji, Shri Irodov ji and Maanniya HC Verma ji, \'Kota Factory\' is TVF\'s latest original. India\'s first \'Black and White\' show highlights the problems present day IIT-JEE aspirants face in their day-to-day lives.
        </item>
        <item>
            From the earliest times, the humanity knows about human-flesh eating monsters, lurking in the darkness to devour an unfortunate soul that does not trust rumors. However, the rumors also mention an elite corps of demon hunters, skilled assassins, killing demons. Demon Slayer focuses on Tanjirou Kamado, who is still very young, but is the only man in his family. One day, Tanjirou decides to go down to the local village to make a little money, selling charcoal. When he returns back, he becomes an unwilling part of these horrifying rumors: his family is slaughtered and the only survivor, his sister Nezuko, is turned into demon. For some reason, Nezuko still acts as a human, which is the reason for Tanjirou to join demon slayers and cure his sister. Will he manage to join the elite corps and cure his sister
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Genre -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_genres">
        <item>Documentary</item>
        <item>Action | Adventure | Drama | Fantasy | Horror | Mystery</item>
        <item>Action | Adventure | Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Action | Comedy | Drama</item>
        <item>Crime | Drama</item>
        <item>Action | Comedy | Crime | Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Biography | Drama | History</item>
        <item>Drama | History | Thriller</item>
        <item>Comedy | Drama</item>
        <item>Animation | Action | Fantasy | Thriller</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Language -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_language">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Hindi</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Hindi</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->
    <!-- Release -->
    <string-array name="tv_db_releases">
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- - -->


    <!-- Data Movie -->
    <!-- Title -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_title">
        <item>The Shawsank Redemtion</item>
        <item>The God Father</item>
        <item>The God Father: Part II</item>
        <item>The Dark Knight</item>
        <item>The Irishmen</item>
        <item>Joker</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Avengers: Endgame</item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</item>
        <item>Klaus</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Image Name   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_image">
        <!-- The Shawsank Redemtion -->
        <item>@drawable/the_shawshank_redemption</item>

        <!-- The God Father -->
        <item>@drawable/the_god_father</item>

        <!-- The God Father: Part II -->
        <item>@drawable/the_god_father_2</item>

        <!-- The Dark Knight -->
        <item>@drawable/the_dark_knight</item>

        <!-- The Irishmen -->
        <item>@drawable/the_irisman</item>

        <!-- Joker -->
        <item>@drawable/joker</item>

        <!-- Avengers: Infinity War -->
        <item>@drawable/infinity_war</item>

        <!-- Avengers: Endgame -->
        <item>@drawable/endgame</item>

        <!-- Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Vers -->
        <item>@drawable/spiderman</item>

        <!-- Klaus -->
        <item>@drawable/klaus</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Rating   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_ratings">
        <item>9.2</item>
        <item>9.1</item>
        <item>9.0</item>
        <item>9.0</item>
        <item>8.1</item>
        <item>8.6</item>
        <item>8.4</item>
        <item>8.4</item>
        <item>8.4</item>
        <item>8.4</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Rating Release  -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_releases">
        <item>1994</item>
        <item>1972</item>
        <item>1974</item>
        <item>2008</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Overview   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_overviews">
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview01</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview02</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview03</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview04</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview05</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview06</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview07</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview08</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview09</item>
        <item>@string/data_movie_overview10</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Storyline   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_storylines">
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline01</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline02</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline03</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline04</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline05</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline06</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline07</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline08</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline09</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_storyline10</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- Genres   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_genres">
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres01</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres02</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres03</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres04</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres05</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres06</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres07</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres08</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres09</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_genres10</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <!-- language   -->
    <string-array name="movie_db_languages">
        <item>@string/data_movies_language01</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language02</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language03</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language04</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language05</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language06</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language07</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language08</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language09</item>
        <item>@string/data_movies_language10</item>
    </string-array>
    <!---->
</resources>